[{
	"activityType":"quiz",
	"title":"Answer the following questions",
	"quizDescription":[{"text":"For each of the expressions below, specify its type and value. If it generates an error, select type 'NoneType' and put the word 'error' in the box for the value.<br><br>Assume we've made the following assignment:"},
	{"code":"tuples2.py"},
	{"attachment":["tuples2.py"]},
	{"text":"Additionally, assume that the expressions are evaluated in the order shown - that is, each problem part is evaluated directly after the previous problem part(s)."}
	],
	"questions":
	[
		{
			"questionType" : "fillintheblank",
			"questionText": "Value of the expression? <br> <code>x[0]</code>",
			"points":"1",
			"answer":"1"
		},
		{
			"questionType" : "dropdown",
			"questionText": "Type of the expression?  <br> <code>x[0]</code>",
			"points":"1",
			"dropdown":
				{
					"option":["NoneType","int","float","boolean","function","string","tuple","list"],
					"correct":"int"
				}
		},
		{
			"questionType" : "fillintheblank",
			"questionText": "Value of the expression? <br> <code>x[2]</code>",
			"points":"1",
			"answer":"[3, 'John', 4]"
		},
		{
			"questionType" : "dropdown",
			"questionText": "Type of the expression?  <br> <code>x[2]</code>",
			"points":"1",
			"dropdown":
				{
					"option":["NoneType","int","float","boolean","function","string","tuple","list"],
					"correct":"list"
				}

		},
		{
			"questionType" : "fillintheblank",
			"questionText": "Value of the expression? <br> <code>x[-1]</code>",
			"points":"1",
			"answer":"'Hi'"
		},
		{
			"questionType" : "dropdown",
			"questionText": "Type of the expression?  <br> <code>x[-1]</code>",
			"points":"1",
			"dropdown":
				{
					"option":["NoneType","int","float","boolean","function","string","tuple","list"],
					"correct":"string"
				}
		},
		{
			"questionType" : "fillintheblank",
			"questionText": "Value of the expression? <br> <code>x[2][2]</code>",
			"points":"1",
			"answer":"4"
		},
		{
			"questionType" : "dropdown",
			"questionText": "Type of the expression?  <br> <code>x[2][2]</code>",
			"points":"1",
			"dropdown":
				{
					"option":["NoneType","int","float","boolean","function","string","tuple","list"],
					"correct":"int"
				}
		},
		{
			"questionType" : "fillintheblank",
			"questionText": "Value of the expression? <br> <code>x[0:1]</code>",
			"points":"1",
			"answer":"[1]"
		},
		{
			"questionType" : "dropdown",
			"questionText": "Type of the expression?  <br> <code>x[0:1]</code>",
			"points":"1",
			"dropdown":
				{
					"option":["NoneType","int","float","boolean","function","string","tuple","list"],
					"correct":"list"
				}

		},
		{
			"questionType" : "fillintheblank",
			"questionText": "Value of the expression? <br> <code>2 in x</code>",
			"points":"1",
			"answer":"True"
		},
		{
			"questionType" : "dropdown",
			"questionText": "Type of the expression?  <br> <code>2 in x</code>",
			"points":"1",
			"dropdown":
				{
					"option":["NoneType","int","float","boolean","function","string","tuple","list"],
					"correct":"boolean"
				}
		},
		{
			"questionType" : "fillintheblank",
			"questionText": "Value of the expression? <br> <code>3 in x</code>",
			"points":"1",
			"answer":"False"
		},
		{
			"questionType" : "dropdown",
			"questionText": "Type of the expression?  <br> <code>3 in x</code>",
			"points":"1",
			"dropdown":
				{
					"option":["NoneType","int","float","boolean","function","string","tuple","list"],
					"correct":"boolean"
				}

		},
		{
			"questionType" : "fillintheblank",
			"questionText": "Value of the expression? <br> <code>x[0]=8</code>",
			"points":"1",
			"answer":"[8, 2, [3, 'John', 4], 'Hi'] "
		},
		{
			"questionType" : "dropdown",
			"questionText": "Type of the expression?  <br> <code>x[0]=8</code>",
			"points":"1",
			"dropdown":
				{
					"option":["NoneType","int","float","boolean","function","string","tuple","list"],
					"correct":"list"
				}
		}
	]
}]
